

### **ABOUT ME**

I'm an impact-driven product designer with over five years of multinational experience in various industries. My passion lies in crafting meaningful and impactful digital products. I also strive to help brands improve their digital experiences that address user needs and business goals.

## **TECH SKILLS**

DESIGN DEVELOPMENT TOOLS

Figma HTML/CSS
Sketch Javascript/jQuery
Adobe CC Google Analytics
Principle Git/GitHub
Overflow Zeplin

Hotjar

#### COMPETENCIES

Visual Design
Experience Design
Interaction Design
Interface Design
Product Strategy

Miro

Wireframing Prototyping Info Architecture Design System User Testing

## **EDUCATION**

# SIMON FRASER UNIVERSITY

B/A - Interactive Arts + Technology Design Concentration

Graduated with Distinction and Co-op Education Award 2014 - 2019

## **ACHIEVEMENTS**

#### **DEAN'S HONOR ROLL**

FALL 2014

Awarded to students for achieving a 3.50 (out of 4.33) or higher GPA.

#### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

## Senior Product Designer / Tokoplas

SEP 2020 - PRESENT

- Working together with management and engineers to redefine the user experience of the e-commerce website, seller portal, and mobile apps.
- Leading the design efforts of the new website and seller portal as well as creating design system, mockups, and prototypes for development.

### UX/UI Designer / Zaui Software

DEC 2019 - APR 2020

- Collaborated with engineers and product experts to design flows and features for the new web booking engine and back-office platform.
- Developed wireframes, high-fidelity mockups, and interactive prototypes for the new web booking engine and back-office platform.

## Digital Designer / PayByPhone

OCT 2018 - APR 2019

- Redefined the user experience and designed the interface of the new parking operators (B2B) and careers pages.
- Produced marketing materials for print and digital such as promotional banners, posters, postcards, display ads, and social media graphics.

### UX/UI Designer / BSTRO

MAY - SEP 2018

- Collaborated with senior designers and developers in designing digital experiences for Johnson & Johnson, Chef Software, The San Francisco Marathon, and two other startup clients.
- Day-to-day included creative concepting, competitive analysis, sitemap drafting, wireframing, mockups design, and prototyping.

#### UX/UI Designer / BuzzIt Inc.

SEP 2017 - AUG 2018

- Worked collaboratively with a product manager and a developer in redesigning Buzzlt's website and mobile apps in a startup environment.
- Overhauled the visual design and user experience of the entire Android & iOS app by producing 50+ sets of end to end mockups.

## UX/UI Designer / GenomeMe

JAN - AUG 2017

- Completed the development of GenomeMe's major web redesign project.
- Designed layouts, streamlined flows, icons, and interactions for over 20+ responsive web pages and developed them using Foundation framework.